hi everyone welcome to the Java 11
大家好，欢迎来到Java 11
overview session my name is banal the
概述会议，我叫banal
traverse' I am the vice president of
遍历“我是
engineering of the Java platform I am
我是Java平台的工程
responsible for the Java SE development
负责Java SE开发
I have been working on the Java platform
我一直在Java平台上工作
since 1998 and I've managed Java
自1998年以来，我一直管理Java
platform development since Java 7 first
自Java 7首次开发平台以来
we'll talk about the new six months with
我们将讨论新的六个月
each other
彼此
second we will provide an overview of
其次，我们将概述
the new features introduced in Java 11
Java 11中引入的新功能
third we will discuss the key advantages
第三，我们将讨论主要优势
to upgrade to Java 11 4 we will discuss
升级到Java 11 4，我们将讨论
the recently introduced new monthly Java
最近推出的新的每月Java
AC support subscriptions free gdk9 the
AC支持订阅免费的gdk9
really sacred cycle four major gdka
真正神圣的周期四大gdka
thesis was about to use while we plan
我们计划时论文将要使用
for three years as it is unfortunately
三年了，因为很不幸
the case with large and complex feature
具有大而复杂特征的情况
driven project we ended up dealing the
驱动项目，我们最终处理了
release by more than 12 months to ensure
放行超过12个月，以确保
that the long fall features lambda in
漫长的秋天里有lambda
PDA in module in gdk9 we're fully done
gdk9模块中的PDA我们已经完全完成
while this word is model work work well
虽然这个词是模型工作正常
for Java for many years the advance of
Java多年来的进步
modern have developed the requirement
现代已发展了要求
for more frequent software grade due to
由于更频繁的软件等级
security concerns and the industry
安全问题和行业
trying to use continuous integration
尝试使用持续集成
system with both frequent upgrades have
经常升级的系统都有
led us to explore the faster and more
引导我们探索更快，更多
predictable with his model for job al
用他的工作模型可以预测
Jessica Curran you know what recently
杰西卡·柯兰（Jessica Curran）
the software industry has discovered
软件行业已经发现
that's more and frequent update me to
这是我经常更新的
make feature delivery was faster and
使功能交付更快，并且
safer Java is no exception in agreement
更安全的Java也不例外
with the open JDK community we moved to
通过开放的JDK社区，我们移至
a six months with it again while we were
六个月后，我们再次
moving to the six months with his
搬到他的六个月
guidance we also took the opportunities
指导我们也抓住了机会
to revamp the JDK version the barracks
修改军营的JDK版本
we set on on the simple numbering scheme
我们基于简单的编号方案
that increase the major it is number by
增加专业是数字
one for each six months with this
每六个月一个
general scheme allow us to deliver
总体方案使我们能够交付
Java language productivity improvements
Java语言生产力的提高
in the six months with by Jesse Pierrot
在六个月内与杰西·皮耶罗（Jesse Pierrot）
language changes to the Java
语言对Java的更改
specifications requires a hearse to
规格要求
increase the majority's number beside
在旁边增加多数数
the challenge to move from eight to nine
从八到九的挑战
the overall feedback is that people we
总体反馈是，我们
moved to nine found the move to 10
移至9发现移至10
trivial for instance Heidi supported the
举个例子，海蒂（Heidi）支持
new box and text features and producing
新的框和文本功能以及制作
GDK 10 by the launch it is still early
GDK 10的发布还为时过早
has a co system need to transition to
有一个共同系统需要过渡到
the new model but we remain optimistic
新模式，但我们仍然乐观
the new six months where this cadence
新六个月的节奏
will continue to be successful while we
我们将继续成功
were considering a faster release
正在考虑发布更快的版本
cadence we also acknowledge the need for
节奏，我们也承认
most people in long term support already
大多数长期支持的人已经
many enterprise workload are likely to
许多企业的工作负载可能会
need more time to uptake new javadi's
需要更多时间来吸收新的javadi
to address this concern we decided to
为了解决这个问题，我们决定
identify roughly every three years at
大约每三年确定一次
six months Chris Callen as a long term
六个月的克里斯·卡伦（长期）
supported with this model of six months
六个月的模型支持
and long term or LTS releases is not new
而且长期发行或LTS发行不是新的
within our industry and is already being
在我们的行业中并且已经
used by many software distribution such
被许多软件发行所使用，例如
as Linux so in summary six months
作为Linux，总结六个月
queries are all about rapid paced of
查询都是关于快节奏的
innovations improve performance and
创新可以提高绩效并
continuous integration LTS releases are
持续集成LTS版本是
all about long-term commitment to
关于长期致力于
provide stability and security updates
提供稳定性和安全性更新
y12 provides users as we are changing
y12为我们不断变化的用户
the radius model we also saw that this
半径模型我们也看到了
was the right time to address feedback
是解决反馈的合适时机
on the Java busier life the binary card
Java繁忙生活中的二进制卡
license or BCL has been the predominant
许可证或BCL占主导地位
license for the java technology for
Java技术的许可证
we're over ready to clarify licensing
我们已经准备好澄清许可
going forward
向前走
oracle will now be producing true
甲骨文现在将产生真实
I don't recall GDK distributions out of
我不记得GDK发行版了吗
the same OpenJDK source code for all the
所有相同的OpenJDK源代码
platform usable
平台可用
oracle open JDK will be available under
oracle open JDK将在
the GPL license for free or user
免费或用户的GPL许可证
normally accustomed to the PCL
通常习惯于PCL
Oracle JDK ladies under the Oracle
Oracle下的Oracle JDK女士
commercial license for commercial
商业许可证
shipping this transition is going very
运输这种过渡非常顺利
well and we are now producing Oracle
好，我们现在正在生产Oracle
OpenJDK bills and all conceded in Oracle
OpenJDK帐单和所有在Oracle中被承认的帐单
GDP since Billiken we are now 99% there
自Billiken以来的GDP，我们现在达到了99％
with the conversion between Oracle open
与Oracle之间的转换打开
GDP and Oracle GDP which is a common
GDP和Oracle GDP是常见的
misunderstanding on Oracle JDK 11 go in
对Oracle JDK 11的误解
commercial and Java not being free
商业和Java不是免费的
anymore is that now we are also
不再是现在我们也是
producing or I call up Angelique liberal
制作或我致电Angelique Liberty
and they are the free DP allies so you
他们是免费的DP盟友，所以您
should consider the new oracle open JDK
应该考虑新的oracle打开JDK
build as all public update in fact they
建立为所有事实上的公共更新
are always been a six month with his
和他在一起总是六个月
guidance for the GDP it was just number
GDP指导数字
different when you went from 80 20 80 40
从80 20 80 40开始时有所不同
to 80 60 then you were on the six months
到80 60那你就六个月了
with its balance of roughly the same
其平衡大致相同
scope so you need to consider the free
范围，因此您需要考虑免费
for record open JDK 12 13 and 14 radius
用于记录打开的JDK 12 13和14半径
has all numbering 11 2011 update 40 and
具有所有编号11 2011更新40和
11 ellipses yes
11个椭圆是
Java is did free JDK 11 is delivering 17
Java是免费的JDK 11正在交付17
new major features I will not cover all
新的主要功能我将不介绍所有
the new feature in this video I
这部影片的新功能
encourage you to watch the other video
鼓励您观看其他视频
we have published on this chart besides
我们已经在这张图表上发布了
internal JVM feature to improve the
内部JVM功能改进
efficiency of the GBM such as jab 181
GBM的效率，例如戳戳181
nest based access control
基于嵌套的访问控制
Jeb 209 dynamic constant I want to
我想要的Jeb 209动态常数
mention Jeb 321
提到杰布321
the new HTTP stack that is graduating
即将毕业的新HTTP堆栈
from being an incubator of features and
从成为功能的孵化器和
will significantly improve HTTP
将大大改善HTTP
performance
性能
Jeb 331 provide low very profiling and
Jeb 331提供了非常低的轮廓
is a contribution from Google as we
是Google的贡献，因为我们
announced we are removing Kaba in Java
宣布我们将删除Java中的Kaba
EE component from GE
GE的EE组件
kolba in the Java EE module we still be
Java EE模块中的kolba仍然是
available as separate module to ensure
作为单独的模块提供，以确保
smooth
光滑
visions to our Java EE users we also
对我们的Java EE用户的构想
another announcing in j11 our intent to
J11中另一个宣布我们的意图
deprecated national in fact one now that
现在已经过时的国民
Java has a module system we can more
Java有一个模块系统，我们可以更多
clearly separate optional module from
明确将可选模块与
the core platform and let those modules
核心平台，让那些模块
evolve at their own pace
按照自己的节奏发展
Angelica 11 we are introducing a new
当归11我们正在推出新的
feature to simplify on-ramp of new Java
简化新Java入门的功能
developers aggeliki 11 allow you to
aggeliki 11开发人员可让您
launch single Java source file from a
从一个启​​动单个Java源文件
single command instead of the previous 2
单个命令，而不是前两个
step compile and then run this is going
一步编译，然后运行
in the direction to reduce a friction
减少摩擦的方向
for new developers launcher we are very
对于新开发者启动器，我们非常
excited to introducing GD 11 an
激动地推出GD 11
experimental new low latency G's jab 333
实验性新低延迟G戳戳333
VG's VDC implement a novel approach to
VG的VDC实现了一种新颖的方法
tease enabling for concurrent
逗弄并发
collections with smart with barriers
智慧与障碍的集合
that will allow to deliver predictable a
可以提供可预测的
very low past time of a few milliseconds
过去几毫秒的时间很短
at the scale of a multi terabyte all
全部都在TB级
these with only a small swoop with
这些只有一小撮
reductions less than 15 pose delivering
减少少于15个姿势
that GC required us to look at the
GC要求我们查看
entire JVM Layton's GC one time in
一次整个JVM Layton的GC
compiler we are very excited about the
编译器让我们感到非常兴奋
future that the GC will enable by taking
GC将采取的未来
into account hardware memory latency
考虑到硬件内存延迟
characteristic to optimize object
优化对象的特征
locations in different regions of
在不同地区的位置
security is an issue
安全是一个问题
essential part in critical element of
关键要素的关键部分
the Java block we are massively
我们大规模的Java区块
investing in security to keep the Java
投资安全性以保留Java
platform sick jab 332
平台生病的刺戳332
is implementing TLS 1.3 TLS 1.3 is a
正在实施TLS 1.3 TLS 1.3是
major overall of the TLS protocol and
TLS协议的主要整体
provide significant security and
提供重要的安全性
performance
性能
Kilis wounded 3 superseded previous
Kilis受伤3被先前取代
version of TLS including version 1 that
TLS版本，包括版本1
we are very pleased also to follow
我们也很高兴跟随
through on our commitment to an open
通过我们对开放的承诺
source the java fly recorder commercial
来源Java fly Recorder商业版
features java fly recorder provides
Java fly Recorder提供的功能
extremely low average for filing
平均极低的申请
capabilities blaze and Windows of filing
功能创新和归档窗口
bill deep inside the JVM energy always
始终在JVM能量内深入计费
on in production deployment for
在生产部署中
mission-critical Rockler in more
关键任务Rockler更多
accurate allocation for fighting with
准确分配与
automatic memory leak detection the
自动内存泄漏检测
great features there are so many reasons
很棒的功能有很多原因
why you want to upgrade to GDP level
为什么要升级到GDP水平
especially if you are still on GD GD
尤其是如果您还在使用GD GD
cannot nine dedicate an energy TP 11
不能九个专用能量TP 11
introduced significant stability
引入了显着的稳定性
functionally and performance
功能和性能
improvements compared to GDP to name a
与GDP相比的改善
few
几个
compact string is reducing footprint and
紧凑的琴弦减少了占地面积，
start up to 30% of reductions in 20%
开始减少30％，减少20％
star c2g compiler crypto intrinsic from
star c2g编译器crypto固有
Intel up to 30% crypto government
英特尔最高30％的加密货币政府
support overall g1 improvement as g1
支持g1的总体改进
become the default GC engine in AI
成为AI中的默认GC引擎
application class data sharing up to 30%
应用程序类数据共享高达30％
star of improvement in 20% footprint
占地20％的改进之星
reductions another commercial feature
减少了另一个商业特征
that we open source making java mode we
我们开源了Java模式
highly recommend that your great to GDP
强烈建议您对GDP表示赞赏
we are very pleased to recently
我们最近很高兴
introduced a new simplified an
推出了新的简化版
affordable Java EE support subscription
负担得起的Java EE支持订阅
to our enterprise customers the new
给我们的企业客户新的
pricing model is $25 cameras per
定价模式为每台相机$ 25
processors for servers $2.50 per month
服务器的处理器$ 2.50每月
per user for desta significant discount
每位用户可获得desta大幅折扣
is available for large deployments you
可用于大型部署
for example if you are looking up to
例如，如果您正在寻找
20,000 processor support if we
20,000个处理器支持，如果我们
discounted at 50% of $12 in people we
在我们的用户中以12美元的50％折扣
are ready making java support affordable
准备使Java支持负担得起
to everyone into our customers you can
给每个人我们的客户
find more informations on the provided
查找有关提供的更多信息
why choosing oracle for commercial
为什么选择Oracle商业版
support simply because you want support
支持只是因为您想要支持
from the ste world of the Java platform
来自Java平台的ste world
the company that is leading the
领导该公司的公司
development of Java in of NDK and as a
NDK中Java的开发
deepest expertise to address any of you
最深的专业知识来解决你们中的任何一个
mission critical issues in all areas of
各个领域的关键任务问题
the platform from client security to
从客户端安全到
library GBM GC a runtime JIT compiler of
库GBM GC的运行时JIT编译器
serviceability in language more than 90%
语言的可服务性超过90％
of the development of the Java platform
Java平台的开发
is done by Oracle engineers in open GDP
由Oracle工程师在开放GDP中完成
you will get access to performance
您将获得性能
stability and the update directly from
稳定性和更新直接来自
Oracle
甲骨文
beyond JDK demand support you will also
除了JDK的需求支持之外，您还将
get access to GT key eight and seventy
可以使用GT钥匙八和七十
three updates 24 by 7 support and access
3个更新，每24个7支持和访问
to critical bug fixes before they get
对重要的错误修复程序进行修复
included in publicly available base all
包含在所有公开资料库中
these with a simple monthly subscription
这些只需简单的每月订阅
prices pay as you use and pay as your
价格按照您使用的方式支付，按您的价格支付
business is going in summary we have
总而言之，我们的业务发展顺利
accelerated the pace of innovation for
加快了创新的步伐
Java with six months with ease while
Java轻松六个月
providing stability security and
提供稳定的安全性和
commitment to enterprise users before I
我对企业用户的承诺
cordially key idea skills GDK 11 is
诚挚的关键思想技能GDK 11是
packed with innovations security for the
充满了创新的安全性
DVD and performance we have follow up on
DVD和性能我们会跟进
our commitment to open source all our
我们致力于开源我们所有的
commercial features gf4 obsidian and
商业功能gf4黑曜石和
edges and make java more open and free
优势，使Java更开放，更自由
we have simplified
我们简化了
Java licensing by transitioning out of
通过过渡出Java许可
the BCA license and delivering now but
BCA许可证并立即交付，但
oracle open GD key under of the free GPL
oracle在免费GPL下打开GD密钥
license and oracle GDP and their
许可证和Oracle GDP及其
commercial license for commercial
商业许可证
support yes we shall buy continues to be
支持，我们将继续购买
free we introduced a new support
免费，我们推出了新的支持
subscriptions to make Java long-term
订阅使Java成为长期合作伙伴
support more affordable to everyone
支持每个人都负担得起的
beyond Java 11 we have a very solid and
除了Java 11，我们还有一个非常扎实的
exciting technical one I would like to
我想要的令人兴奋的技术
take this opportunity to especially
借此机会特别
thank everyone that contributed to GE 11
感谢为GE 11做出贡献的所有人
let's continue to innovate in advance in
让我们继续在
Java platform together thanks for
Java平台一起感谢
watching
观看